{
    "subject": "resource/Ra\u00fal_Silva_Henr\u00edquez",
    "predicate": "property/title",
    "object": "Bishop of Valpara\u00edso",
    "human_readable": "Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez is titled 'Bishop of Valpara\u00edso'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8725751042366028,
            "question": "Where is Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez the Bishop of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8194355964660645,
            "question": "Who is Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8168221116065979,
            "question": "What title is Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez known by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6065075397491455,
            "question": "Is Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez a religious figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5427843928337097,
            "question": "What city or region is associated with Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez's title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49172914028167725,
            "question": "What position does Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez hold in the Catholic Church?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4034232199192047,
            "question": "What does the title 'Bishop' signify in Catholicism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33077988028526306,
            "question": "What is the significance of being a Bishop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.299952894449234,
            "question": "Can you name a prominent Chilean Bishop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10703328996896744,
            "question": "Are there any notable historical figures who held this title?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez is titled 'Bishop of Valpara\u00edso'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1282_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a prominent Chilean Bishop?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1282_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of being a Bishop?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1282_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the title 'Bishop' signify in Catholicism?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1282_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1282_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1282/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt, Raul Henriquez was appointed Bishop of Valpara\u00edso by Pope John XXIII on 24 October, 1959."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez served as Bishop of Valpara\u00edso from 1959 to 1961.\" Therefore, the statement that Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez is titled 'Bishop of Valpara\u00edso' is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}